William Giammona

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

Co-founder of GlobalWebThree DAO, a boutique Wyoming-based Decentralized Autonomous Organization focusing on front-end development, blockchain technology, and smart contract creation . As a front-end developer, my expertise spans TypeScript, React, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, UI/UX collaboration, as well as Solidity, Python, Moralis, Ethers.js, Hardhat, Truffle, and Foundry.

Employment History

Co-Founder GlobalWebThree DAO

2022 - PRESENT

Co-founder of GlobalWebThree DAO, a boutique Decentralized Autonomous Organization focusing on on blockchain technology, smart contract creation and front-end development. My work encompasses a diverse array of smart contract creation, including Escrow, Raffle, MultiSig, and NFT based smart contracts, as well as integrating them with front-ends.

Mathematics Tutor, Wyzant

2018 - 2022

At Wyzant, an online tutoring platform, I served as a Mathematics tutor specializing in Trigonometry/Pre-Calculus, Algebra 2, and Geometry. Leveraging my comprehensive understanding of these subjects, I simplified complex concepts and developed individualized learning strategies for students.

Financial Tax Associate, Ernst & Young, San Francisco

2017

At EY, I primarily worked on preparing K-1 tax information for financial LLP's including hedge-funds, private-equity funds, and venture-capital funds. In addition to working with partnerships, I also worked on federal and state corporate tax returns for the Charles Schwab Corporation.

Education

B.A. Economics and Accounting, University of California, Santa Barbara

Electrical Engineering Program, Tel Aviv University, Tel Aviv

2019 - 2021

Courses

Free Code Camp Full Stack Web3 Development Course, 2022

Details

+972535698285

wgiammona@gmail.com

PLACE OF BIRTH

United States

Links

GlobalWebThree Website

<u>Github</u>

Skills

Next.js

React.js

Typescript

Tailwind CSS

HTML & CSS

Foundry

Hardhat

Truffle

Solidity

Python

Ethers.js

Moralis

Languages

English (Native)

Spanish